const dataSet = [
    {
      question: "What is 8 x 1?",
      answers: [
        "1",
        "8",
        "16",
        "9"
      ],
      correct: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Steve Jobs?",
          answers: [
            "CEO of Microsoft",
            "Barber in NY",
            "Movie Star",
            "CEO of Apple"
          ],
          correct: 3
    },
     {
          question: "Metallica is a ____ band",
          answers: [
            "Blues",
            "Hard-Rock",
            "Jazz",
            "Metal"
          ],
          correct: 3
        },
        {
          question: "IS is a ____",
          answers: [
            "Word",
            "Band",
            "Terror Group",
            "Brand"
          ],
          correct: 2
        },
        {
          question: "Who was Einstein",
          answers: [
            "A Scientist",
            "A Dentist",
            "A Serial Killer",
            "None of the above"
          ],
          correct: 0
        },
        {
          question: "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
          answers: [
            "Back-End",
            "Front-End",
            "ReactJS",
            "All of the Above"
          ],
          correct: 3
        },
        {
          question: "Hitler was a",
          answers: [
            "Mass Murderer",
            "Dictator",
            "Jew",
            "None of the above",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          correct: 4
        },
        {
          question: "Korn is a",
          answers: [
            "Nu-Metal band",
            "Religion",
            "Singer"
          ],
          correct: 0
        },
        {
          question: "Windows computers are",
          answers: [
            "Horrible",
            "Great",
            "Cheap",
            "Invented by Bill Gates"
          ],
          correct: 3
        },
        {
          question: "The BigBan stands in",
          answers: [
            "Egypt",
            "London",
            "Amsterdam",
            "NewYork"
          ],
          correct: 1
        },
  ];